Seidenberg, Jacob Additional Arbitration Records 5605
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Records
1864-1977
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Seidenberg, Jacob
5605
11 cubic feet
11 linear ft.
Records.
The bulk of the collection consists of arbitration case files, chiefly in the railroad industry, presented before other industries (most notably the airline industry) and unions (most notably the International Brotherhood of Teamsters), also data collected by Seidenberg for an injunction study of the New York courts, as well as proceedings, transcriprts, and exhibits of two Presidential Emergency Boards on which Seidenberg served.
2297042
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 12, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, January 20, 2016
Biographical / Historical
Dr. Jacob Seidenberg (1914-1996) was a government official who specialized in labor arbitration and non-discrimination contracts, and wrote extensively on labor law and negotiations. He graduated from Temple University in 1937 and received a law degree from the University of Pennsylvania Law School in 1941. During the 1940s he was an attorney with the U.S. War Department, the National War Labor Board and the National Wage Stabilization Board. In 1948 he went to graduate school at Cornell University, from which he earned his Ph.D. in industrial and labor relations in 1951. In 1951 he joined the staff of the President's Committee on Government Contract Compliance. The Committee was abolished by President Dwight D. Eisenhower in August 1953 by Executive Order 10479 and was succeeded by the President's Committee on Government Contracts. Seidenberg was appointed Executive Director of the new committee and served until January 1960 when he resigned to become a full-time labor arbitrator. The Committee was responsible for enforcing non-discrimination clauses in government contracts, worked with private businesses to help them overcome job discrimination, and developed educational programs against ethnic and racial discrimination. The chairman was Vice President Richard Nixon, and the vice chairman was Secretary of Labor James P. Mitchell. In later years Seidenberg served on a number of boards of inquiry involving labor disputes. From 1970 to 1975 he was chairman of the Federal Services Impasses Panel which settled deadlocks in federal labor negotiations.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5007: U.S. Emergency Board No. 175 Transcripts and Exhibits 5032: Jacob Seidenberg Injunction Study 5217: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Case Files
Arbitration, Industrial -- Airlines -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Automobile industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Building trades -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Civil service -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Health facilities -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Machine industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Meat industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Railroads -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Steel industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- Trucking industry -- United States; Arbitration, Industrial -- White collar workers -- United States; Employees, Dismissal of -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Hours of labor -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Labor discipline -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Labor injunctions -- Law and legislation -- New York (State); Mediation and conciliation, Industrial -- Railroads -- United States; Seniority, Employee -- Law and legislation -- United States; Wages -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Wages -- Mediation and conciliation, Industrial -- United States; Wages -- Railroads -- United States; Work assignments -- Arbitration, Industrial -- United States; Employee rules -- United States; AFSCME; Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America; Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Company; Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (U.S.); Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen; Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees; Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen; Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen; Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employes; Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul Railway Company; Eastern Air Lines, Inc.; Erie-Lackawanna Railroad Company; Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders' International Union; Illinois Central Gulf Railroad Company; International Air Line Pilots Association; International Association of Machinists; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America; Long Island Railroad Company; Monongahela Railway Company; National Railway Labor Conference (U.S.); National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; Norfolk and Western Railway Company; Office and Professional Employees International Union; Penn Central Transportation Company; Southern Buffalo Railway Company; Southern Pacific Company; St. Louis Southwestern Railway Company; Switchmen's Union of North America; Union Pacific Railway Company; United States. Congress. Senate. Committee on Labor and Public Welfare. Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations; United Steelworkers of America; United Transportation Union; Western Maryland Railway Company; Boyd, Robert O. (Robert Osborne), 1903-1976; Coburn, William H.; Gill, Lewis M.; Seibel, Lawrence E.; Seidenberg, Jacob, 1914-; Valtin, Rolf
2297042
- Blue Diamond Company Local 557 - 1BT, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Georgetown University NUHC Employee AAA 1630010376, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- CCC(Ingenfelder) Carpenter Historical Council of Washington, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- A&P - IBT - Local 229 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- P.L. Board 1688 PC-RYA, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- P.L. Board no. 1783 Conrail Corp. - UTU (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Greenwich Home&Nursing - NUHE Dist. 99, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- P.L. Board - UTU - L.A. Terminal, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- EAL-IAM SBA 9-76 (MUN02), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Bd. Of Ed. Of Charles County and Ed. Assoc. of Charles County, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Bd. Of Education of Anne Arundel County and Teacher's Assoc. of Ann Arundel AAA 1639015575, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- SBA #853 - Erie Lackawanna - UTU, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- P.L. Board no. 1638 Pittsburgh Lake Erie - RYA, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- ET & WNC Transportation Co. - Local 557 - IBT, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Allegheny Pepsi Cola Bottling co. Retail Store Employer Local 692 FMCS 76K 19035, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- EE0C -AF6E Local 2667 FMCS 76K 12786, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Printing Industry of Wash. D.C. Local 285 - Gain FMCS 76K 12318, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Bon Secours Hospital - West Balt. Community Health Care Corp. Hospital Employer Local 1273, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Printing Industry of Washington D.C. Local 285-Gain FMCS 76K12318, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Georgetown University NUHHC Employees - Dist. 11998 AAA 1630009676, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Dept. of Army (Aberdeen Proving Grounds-IAM(Local2424)) FMCS 76K19190, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Award No. 1732 Case no. 18656, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- PAA - FEIA, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- IBT Local 557 Eastern Express FMCS 73K09029, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Award no. 1746 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Budd Co.- UAW Local 813 AAA 1430033973-M-J, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Prince George County School Board - PGC Education Association, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- FMSC 73K09133 OPEIU - Local 2 - Industry Welfare and Pension Funds, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- O' Bayle Tank Co. - IBT - Local 992 - FMCS 73K09657, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Joseph E. Seagram and Sons - Distillery Workers - Local 34 - FMCS 73K010381, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Navy Dept. - MTC FMCS 75K05093, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Mass Transit Authority (Balt) - OPEIU - Local 2 - AAA - 16-300028-73, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- ILGWU - Perfection Garment AAA 14300183-73S, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- UAW and Wallace-Murray Corp. AAA 1430022772R, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- P.L. Board No. 1009 UTU(C) - Central Railroad of N.J., 1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Bio-Brac Amtrak 40222 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- ALPA-76-72 EAL-30-73 ALPA 10-72 EAL 2-72 Mowry, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- P.L. Board No. 1074 PC-Brac (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Chicago - Northwestern BRAC Amtrak, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- American Federation of Television and Radio Artists - Station WFBR(radio) AAA 1430041072C, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- P.L. Board No. 955 - PC -BLE(New Haven), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- House Electric Company Electric Utility Employee Union FMCS 73K08155, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- P.L. Board no. 1112 NW-UTU, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- EAL-ALPA, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Scope and Contents
  January 17-18-1973
- Office of Professional Employees Union Local no. 2 IAMAW (Box 2, Folder 20)
- FMCS 73K 04772 MacMillan Bloedel Package L+D UPP Local 925 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Fairfax Education Assoc. - Fairfax County School Board, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Budd Co. HAW AAA 14300657 72M/J, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Horn Express - IBT Local 557, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- George Hyman Construction and Reinforced Iron Workers Local 201 FMCS 74K02309, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- A&P Co. - Retail Clerks Union - Local 278 AAA 1630 002 73, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- P.L. Board No. 321 Great Northern RR- UTU (C), 1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Budd Company - UAW - Local 813 AAA 14300403073-M-J, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Leeds and Northrup - UAW - Local 1350 AAA 1430014173-H, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- EAL-ALPA, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- P.L. Board No. 1090 Detroit and Toledo Shore Line - UTU, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- EAL-IAM-818A-97-73(, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees Local 1199E - Sinai Hospital of Balt. AAA 14300902720, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- FMCS 73K 1266 Premium Distributor - IBT - Local 67, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Gen. Telephone Comm. Workers of America, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- P.L. Board No. 1242 Southern Pacific - BLE, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- P.L. Board No. 965 Portland Terminal - UTU, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- P.L. Board No. 816 Monongahela Connecting - UTU, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- P.L. Board No. 1269 Penn Central (NH) - BLE (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Arlington School Board - AFSME, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Budd Co. - UAW Local 813 AAA 14300243-M-J (Box 3, Folder 19)
- SBA # 838 P.C. - IBT (Airline Aerospace Employees/Local 732), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- ITT Grinnell Corp. Int. Brotherhood of Molders AAA 14300234752, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Piedmont Airlines - IAM, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Wage-Hour Assignment 1968-Puerto Rico (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Northwest Airlines - IAM, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Newport News Designers' Assoc. of N.Y., 1976 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Group Health Association OPEIU - Local no.2, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- 5B Administration - AFGE, Local 2532 FMCS 76K07414 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- P.L. Board No. 1347 E-L-UTU, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- P.L. Board 1348 Western Pacific Railroad - BLE (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Blue Bell Inc. Greensboro N.C., 1973 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Western Electric Co., 1961 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Weirston Steel Co. (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Manhattan Shirt Co., 1864 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- American Tobacco, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Union Carbide Local 109-1UPOW FMCS 72A/9109 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Arbitrator (Box 4, Folder 8)
- AFT-AFL-CIO Committee for Nat'l Representatives, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- AAA 1630001273 - Safeway Stores - Amalgamated Meat Cutters, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Award No. 1795 - P.L. Bd. #969 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- P.L. Board No. 969 Award no. 1796 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- P.L. Board no. 1798 Award no. 1798 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- P.L. Board 1091 BM-BRAC, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- SBA No. 815 NW Del. + Hudson - UTU (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Phila Federation of Teachers - School District of Phila 14390293-73K (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Amstar Corporation - Amalgamated Meat Cutters AAA 16300037-73 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Capitol Unintentional Airbag, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Mutual Broadcasting System - IBEWU AAA 1630012574, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Arundel Corp. - IAM #199 FMCS 74K13261, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Awellan Sales Co. Local 67 - IBT, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Kane Transfer Co. Local 557-187, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Mergentine Corp vs. Carpenter's District Council, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- C&O - UTU - P.L. Board 1468, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- A&P - Local 730 - IBT FMCS 75K 14391, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Public Law BB #1497 SP-BLE, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- P.L. Board no. 1507 - LIRR - BR Corner (Box 5, Folder 10)
- M&M Transportation Co. Local 557 - IBT, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- P.L.B. #1455 - G.C. G. Davis - Submissions (Box 5, Folder 12)
- E-4426 Award no. 55 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Claim E-4759 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Award no. 58 Claim E-4423 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Award no. 59 Claim no. E-4444 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Award no. 60 Case E-4605 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Award no. 61 Claim no. 4722 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Award no. 62 Claim E-4771 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Award no. 63 Case 47286 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Award 64 4786 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Award no. 65 Case E-4793 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Award no. 66 E-4791 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Award no. 67 E-5473 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Award no. 68 E-5502 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Award no. 69 E-5361 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Award no. E-5569 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Award no. 71 E-5549 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Award no. 72 Case no. 4798 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Award no. 73 Case no. 5508 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Award no. 74 Case no. 5638 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Award no. 75 Case no. 5533 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Award no. 76 Case no. 5514 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Award no. 77 Case no. 5518 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Award no. 78 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Award no. 79 Case no. 5517 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Award no. 80 Case no. 5607 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Award no. 81 Case no. 5435 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Award no. 82 Case no. 5462 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Award no. 83 Case no. 5499 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Award no. 84 Case no. 5021 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Award no. 85 Case no. 5357 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Award no. 54 Ostentag Case (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Southwestern Bell Telephone Co. (AAA 71-30-0315-75), 1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Roper-Eastern Products and UFW Local 75 (AAA 14-30-0609-75) (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Hughes Aircraft Co. - Culver City, CA, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- National Vacation Agreements BLF&E 3-E, 1949-1963 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Metropolitan Edison - IBEWU Local 603 (AAA 14-30-0712-75-H), 1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Phila. Bd. Of Education - Phila. Fed. Of Teachers AAA 1439-1174-76-75M, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Merkle Press OPEIU Local 2, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Continental Airlines - racial discrimination in hiring decision, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Louisville and Nashville Railroad Co. (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Consultant Contract (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Maintenance Tech. Service - USWA Local 13714 FMCS 76K02825/2826, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- P.L. Board no. 1183 South Shore and Newburg - UTU (Box 6, Folder 12)
- General Electric - IAM FMCS 72A1 11865 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- P.L. Board no. 900 UP - BLE (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Duke University - AFSCME - Local 77 FMCS 73K009140, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- P.L. Board no. 1184 LV -BLE (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Metropolitan Edison - IBEWU - Local 563 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- P.L. Board no. 1619 - Union Railroad Co. - USWA Local 3263, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- P.L. Board no. 1466 Penn Central - UTU (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Washington Post - ITU Local 75E (Box 6, Folder 20)
- SCM Corp. - USWA Local 14019 FMCS 75K 16208, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- P.L. 61647 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Puerto Rico - W&H Member 1974 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- P.L. Bd. 1455 - EL - UTU, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- United Union AFSCME AAA 1630009574 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- P.L. Board no. 1766 - UTU (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Printing Industries of Washington - Columbia Typographical Union - Local 101 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Construction Contractor Council - Carpenters District Council ( C.J. Cookley co.) (Box 7, Folder 7)
- MC Public Schools MCEA (Box 7, Folder 8)
- A&P Co. Inc. - Local 570 - Warehouse Employees Union - IBT (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Washington Hospital Center - SEIU - Local 722 HC 275-3689B01 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- EAL-24-74 ALPA 16-74 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Special Board of Adjustment #832 - BLE (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Leaseway System - Local 639 - IBT FMCS 75K04155 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- P.L. Board no. 1367 - ATS - BLE (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Environmental Elements Corp. FMCS 75K07235 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Arbitrator (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Roper-Eastern and United Furniture Workers Local 75 AAA 1430107374S (Box 7, Folder 17)
- EAL-IAM SBA 7873 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Construction Contractor Council (Gill election Co,) - Corporation District Council AAA 1630014274 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- PC -BRAC - Arbitration Committee - Article XI May 6,1968 Agreement, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Arbitration Board PC-BRAC (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Southwestern Bell - CWA - AAA 7130018275 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Saturn Airways ALPA -SAT-41-73, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Silver Hill Concrete Co. Local 639 - IBT FMCS 76K14792 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Motor Freight Expression Local 639 - IBT (Box 8, Folder 6)
- P.L. Board 1296 PC - UTU(E), 1975 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- 1975 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- WB Newspaper Guild - Merkle Piers, Inc., 1975 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- SBA - 238-75 EAL-IAM, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Eastern Freightways Local 639-IBT (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Transamerica Freight Local 552-IBT, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Amtrac - 101-CC-2 NRPC-IAMAW (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Public Health Service (HEW), 1976 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Contractors Construction Council and Carpenter's District Council (Box 8, Folder 15)
- B01-HC-4869-70-72-80,81,82 six Hospitals - District 1199E, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- IBPO - Local 442 - Metropolitan Police Dept. of DC AAA 16009476, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- EAL-IAM SBA 855-75, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- WJZ-TV-West Broadcasting Television Broadcasting AAA 1430035576R, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- NY City Commission on Intergroup Relations (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Special Board of Adjustment - Working Agreement - BN - BRAC, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Public Tour Board No. 60 - IAM - Long Island Railroad Co. (Box 9, Folder 2)
- P.L. Board no. 920 - Longview,Portland and Northern Railway - BLE (Box 9, Folder 3)
- P.L. Board no. 818 PRSL - UTU, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Case no. 2 of Special board of Adjustment no. 849 - Norfolk and Western Railway Company and Norfolk and Western-Virginian GCA (UTU) (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Case no. 3 Special Board of Adjustment no. 849 - Norfolk and Western Railway Company and Norfolk and Western-Virginian GCA (UTU) (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Case no. 4 Special Board of Adjustment no. 849 - Norfolk and Western Railway Company and Norfolk and Western-Virginian GCA (UTU) (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Case no. 5 Special Board of Adjustment no. 849 - Norfolk and Western Railway Company and Norfolk and Western-Virginian GCA (UTU) (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Case no.6 Special Board of Adjustment no. 849 - Norfolk and Western Railway Company and Norfolk and Western-Virginian GCA (UTU) (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Case no. 7 Special Board of Adjustment no. 849 - Norfolk and Western Railway Company and Norfolk and Western-Virginian GCA (UTU) (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Case no. 8 Special Board of Adjustment no. 849 - Norfolk and Western Railway Company and Norfolk and Western-Virginian GCA (UTU) (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Case no.9 Special Board of Adjustment no. 849 - Norfolk and Western Railway Company and Norfolk and Western-Virginian GCA (UTU) (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Case no. 10 Special Board of Adjustment no. 849 - Norfolk and Western Railway Company and Norfolk and Western-Virginian GCA (UTU) (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Case no. 11 Special Board of Adjustment no. 849 - Norfolk and Western Railway Company and Norfolk and Western-Virginian GCA (UTU) (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Case no. 12 Special Board of Adjustment no. 849 - Norfolk and Western Railway Company and Norfolk and Western-Virginian GCA (UTU) (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Case no. 13 Special Board of Adjustment no. 849 - Norfolk and Western Railway Company and Norfolk and Western-Virginian GCA (UTU) (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Wage - Hour Division, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- P.L. Board No. 1102 - Belt Railway Co. of Chicago - UTU, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- P.L. Board no. 1339 C&O - BLE (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Raleigh Stores - ACWA - Local 188 FMCS K07282 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- P.L. Board no. 1218, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- PGC Public Schools - PGCEA (Bentley Grievance), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Smith and Solomon Trucking and IBT Local 557 - FMCS 75K07160, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- WMATA - Local 922 - IBT FMCS 76K04815, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Davis Distributing Co. Local 67 IBT-FMCS 74K014939 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- WGL -Int. Union of Gas Workers (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Virginia Chemical FMCS 73K08368 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Safeway Stores - Retail Clerk - Local 400 AAA 1630009773, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Public Schools of N.C. - AFSCME - District Council Co. - Local 2093 AAA 1639006074, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- C.J. Langenfelder & Son and Carpenter's District Council AAA 163007574, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Continental Baking Co. - Local 33 - IBT FMCS 74K0 12628, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- aaa-14 30 0149 70D United Cement Lime and Gypsum Workers Local 92 - Standard Lime and Refactories Operations, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Budd Co. - UAW AAA - 14-30-0521-71-MJ, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Budd Co. - UAW - AAA 14 30 0318-71-MJ, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- P.L. Board no. 592 Cambria and Indiana Railroad- UTU (E) (Box 10, Folder 18)
- National Education Assoc. Staff Org. and National Education Assoc. AAA 16300024 71, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- AAA 1330 076571 Home Publishing Co. - Int. Printing Pressman Union Local 196 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Washington Gas Light Co. - Gas Workers Int. FMCS 71A/3228 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Carpenter District Council and DC Excavation AAA 16300059-74 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- BRC and Burlington Northern (Merger-Agreement), 1976 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Award no. 98 (no claim number), 1966 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Award no. 99 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Award no. 101 -LI-BLE (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Award no. 100 LI-BLE (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Award no. 3 Long Island Railroad and BLE (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Award no. 30 (no claim number) (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Award no. 1 (Hoffman Claim) (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Award no. 4 Claim no. E-5665 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Award no. 53 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- P.L. Board LIRR Boilermakers (Box 11, Folder 10)
- AAA-14-30-0135 73 Budd Co. - UAW, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Joint Exhibits (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Construction Contractors Council and Carpenter District Council (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Otis Elevator Co. (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Abex Corp. - Int Molders and Allied Workers - Local 19 FMCS 76K15341 (Box 11, Folder 15)